



# CONTACT



#### **Phone**

+37256804966



robbegarm@gmail.com



#### **Address**

Maleva Põik 6, Tallinn, Estonia



# **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2020 **Master Of Science** in Engineering TalTech University

2012 - 2018 **Bachelor Of Physics** Yerevan State University



### **COURSES**

HTML/CSS

Udemy Udemy

**JavaScript** 

**React JS** 

Udemy

**TypeScript** 

Udemy



# **LANGUAGES**

C1 C1



## **ABOUT ME**

Highly self-motivated frontend developer with experience in designing, building, and deploying real-world websites. I am very passionate about programming and the web and have learned the necessary skills through multiple online courses. I am interested in a junior frontend developer position.



## WORK EXPERIENCE

> Fullstack Web Developer 11.2022 - current E-Pavement OÜ, Estonia

- · Website and UI design, SEO and deployment
- · Building the frontend using React JS
- Building the backend with Spring Boot(Java)/MySQL
- > Solar Panel Engineer 06.2020 - current E-Pavement OÜ, Estonia
  - Production of solar panels, quality control
  - · Electronics development, PCB soldering
  - Installation, repair and on-site maintenance work
- Frontend Web Developer 08.2022 - 11.2022 Khnami, Estonia (remote)
  - · Website design, SEO and deployment
  - Building the website with HTML5/CSS3/JS(ES6)
- > Robot Operator 03.2020 - 06.2020 Starship OÜ, Estonia
  - · Overseeing delivery robots using special software
  - · Remote operation, logging and reporting of issues

# **MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE**

# **BACKEND WEB FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPMENT DEVELOPMENT** HTML5/CSS3 Java/ Spring Boot JavaScript (ES6) **REST API development** React JS MySQL TypeScript



# **SOFT SKILLS**



#### **PORTFOLIO**

- ✓ Fast learner
- √ Team player
- ✓ Problem solver
- Critical thinker
- √ Time management
- ✓ Self-management

### **GitHub**

www.github.com/RobBegArm

#### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/robbegarm/